Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1935-2002.
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-2002.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dale R. Corson papers, 1935-2002.
3-11-2550
Dale R. Corson
54.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, articles, speeches, newsclippings, notes, minutes, calendars, appointment books, memorabilia, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers of Dale Corson from throughout his career, but especially from the time before and after his provostship and presidency. Major correspondents include E. B. White, Floyd R. Newman, Leslie R. Severinghaus, and Philip Will.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dale R. Corson was born in Pittsburg, Kansas in 1914. He received his B.A. degree from the College of Emporia in 1934, his M.A. from the University of Kansas in 1935, and his Ph.D. in physics from the University of California at Berkeley in 1938. In 1940 he discovered astatine, one of the last missing elements on the Periodic Table, while he was a postdoctoral fellow at Berkeley. He was a staff member at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology Radiation Laboratory from 1941 to 1943, and later served as a technical advisor at Air Force Headquarters in Washington, D.C. At the end of the war, he joined the staff of the Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory. In 1946 he came to Cornell University as an assistant professor of physics and helped design the Cornell Synchrotron. During his time at Cornell, he co-authored a textbook, Introduction to Electromagnetic Fields and Waves. He was appointed associate professor of physics in 1947, became a full professor in 1956, was named chairman of the Physics Department in 1956, and became Dean of the College of Engineering in 1959. Dale Corson served as Provost of the University from 1963 to 1969, becoming Cornell’s eighth president in 1969. He guided the University through the political upheavals and economic troubles of the late 1960s and the 1970s.
In 1977, he resigned his position and was appointed Chancellor of the University, serving in that capacity until 1979. The Medical College was a major focus of his attention during this period.
Upon retiring from the Cornell administration, Corson continued to work as a consultant in the fields of engineering and physics, and he was involved in many national and international efforts. He founded the Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable, and he headed a study sponsored by the National Academy of Sciences, Scientific Communication and National Security (1982). It defined research universities' concern about research areas that are not classified but are deemed militarily useful. He also served as a consultant to the Chinese University Development Project, an initiative funded by the World Bank. He was elected to the National Academy of Engineering in 1981.
He helped to found Kendal at Ithaca, a retirement community, in the 1990s. Throughout his life, he has been an avid amateur photographer, and his work has been exhibited in many settings.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers primarily relating to Corson's teaching, research, and administrative activities prior to his appointment as Provost in 1963 and after resigning from his position as President in 1977. Includes course material from his graduate studies at the University of Kansas, the University of California at Berkeley, and his teaching career at Cornell; notes, papers, and research material from Kansas, Berkeley, the War Department, the Massachusetts Institute of Technology Radiation Laboratory, the Los Alamos National Laboratories, and Cornell; administrative files, including meeting minutes, agendas, programs, and photographs related to the Physics Department, the College of Engineering, the synchrotron, and various other academic units; development and other files relating to the Medical College, corporate and alumni relations, and the Board of Trustees, and to Corson's activities relating to the Library Advisory Council, the Music Committee, the Arecibo Observatory, and Deep Springs College and other educational institutions. Correspondents include E.B. White, Floyd R. Newman, Leslie R. Severinghaus, and Philip Will.
Includes material relating to student activism; race relations on campus and the Vietnam War; the Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable; the Chinese University Development Project; the National Academy of Arts and Sciences and the National Academy of Engineering; and Corson's avocations, including photography and travel and his community activities with Kendal at Ithaca, the Sciencenter, the Tompkins County Trust Company, and the Tower Club.
Collection includes appointment books, diaries, calendars, notebooks, diplomas, awards, memorial documents, invitations, oral history transcripts, and a videotape and program from a 1999 symposium honoring Dr. Corson, "Strategy for a Great Research University."
Also, DVD, videotape and program from "Strategy for a Great Research University: A Symposium Honoring Dale Raymond Corson," December 5-7, 1999. DVD, "The Corson Symposium," produced by the Internet-First University Press, includes an 18-minute video tribute, the speeches at a gala banquet and a luncheon (71 minutes), and the audio for more than 13 major addresses presented at the Symposium, including Frank Rhodes and Hunter Rawlings, as well as photographs of family and friends, and presentations by the Glee Club and chimesmasters. Photographs by Jon Reis of Dale Corson's 90th birthday party, April, 2004.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Corson, Dale R.; Newman, Floyd R. (Floyd Roy), 1890-1990.; Severinghaus, Leslie R.; White, E. B. (Elwyn Brooks), 1899-; Will, Philip, 1906-; Cornell University. President.; Cornell University. Provost.; Cornell University. Tower Club.; Cornell University. Development Office.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University-- Endowments.; Cornell University--Planning.; Cornell University-- Board of Trustees.; Cornell University--Campus Council.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Public relations.; Cornell University-New York Hospital School of Nursing.; Cornell University. Medical College.; Cornell University. Chancellor.; Los Alamos National Laboratory.
Places:
Japan.; China.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/85
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/13186
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/13193
Access Restrictions:
Papers are restricted to the permission of the donor's son, David W. Corson, or his heirs until 2030.
Not all the material in the collection is covered by this guide
RELATED MATERIALS
See also the Dale R. Corson papers 1963-1977, collection #3-11-1665, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA01665
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Boxes: 1-7
Letters of recommendation
Series II. Articles and speeches
Boxes: 8-11
Series III. Research and course materials
Boxes: 12-15, 43
Electromagnetic Fields and Waves
Course materials
Series IV. Cornell administration activities
Boxes: 15-27
Physics and engineering
Cornell academic units
University committees, meetings, reports, etc.
Events
Awards, memorials, and other recognitions
Personnel
Medical College
Trustees
Development and corporate relations
Library Advisory Council (LAC)
Music Committee
Cornell history
Arecibo
Deep Springs/Telluride
Student activism and other Vietnam-era issues
Miscellaneous administration notes
Series V. National and international activities and interests
Boxes: 27-36, mapcase
Higher education files
China
Sub-subseries: Administrative files and correspondence
Sub-subseries: Specialists and project staff
Sub-subseries: Reports
Sub-subseries: Individual universities
Sub-subseries: Conference papers
Sub-subseries: Chinese students and scholars abroad CU/China relations
Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable
Academy activities
Sub-subseries: Scientific Communication and National Security ("Corson Report")
Sub-subseries: Other Academy files
Defense Science Board
Engineers Joint Council
Panel on the Future of Government in New York
Japan-related activities
Other national activities and interests
Series VI. Hobbies and avocations
Boxes: 36-37
Series VII. Community activities
Boxes: 37-39
Kendal at Ithaca
Other community activities
Series VIII. Appointment books, diaries, calendars, and notebooks
Boxes: 39-41
Series IX. Personal material
Boxes: 41, 44
Series X. Photographs and memorabilia
Boxes: 45-47, Map case
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, chron., 1930-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, July (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, June (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, May (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Apr. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Mar. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1978, Jan.-Feb., and n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Nov.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Sept.-Oct. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, July-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, June (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Apr. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Mar. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Feb. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1979, Jan. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Sept. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Aug. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, July (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, June (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, May (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Apr. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Mar. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Feb. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1980, Jan. and n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Sept. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, July-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, June (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, May (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Apr. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Mar. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Feb. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1981, Jan. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Oct-Dec (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Sept (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, July-Aug (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, June (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, May (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Apr. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Mar (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Feb. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1982, Jan. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Dec. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Sept-Nov. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, July- Aug. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, June (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, May (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Mar-Apr. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Feb. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Feb. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Feb. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1983, Jan. and n.d. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Nov-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Oct. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984,Sept. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, June-July (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Apr.-June (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Mar. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Feb. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1984, Jan. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1985, Oct- Dec. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1985, July-Sept. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1985, May-June (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1985, Mar- Apr. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1985, Jan-Feb. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1987, May-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1987, Jan- Apr. and n.d. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, Nov- Dec. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, Sept- Oct. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, July- Aug. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, June (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, May (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1988, Jan- Apr. and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Nov- Dec. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Oct- Nov. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, July- Oct. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Apr.- July (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Mar.- Apr. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Feb. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1989, Jan and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, Nov- Dec. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, Aug- Oct. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, June- July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, Apr.- June (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, Mar-Apr. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1990, Jan- Mar and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, Nov- Dec. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, Oct. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, May- Sept. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, Apr. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, Feb- Mar. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1991, Jan and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Dec. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Nov. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Sept- Oct. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, July (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, June (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, May (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Apr. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Mar. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1992, Jan-Feb. and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, Dec. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, Nov. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, Oct. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, July- Sept. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, June (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, May (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, Apr. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1993, Jan- Mar. and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, Nov-Dec. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, Sept- Oct. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, June-July (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, May (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, Apr. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, Feb-Mar. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1994, Jan and n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1995, July-Dec. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1995, Jan-June and n.d. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, chron., 1996-2001 and n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence re: DRC'S Retirement from Presidency, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11-16)
  - Correspondence Re: DRC'S Retirement from Presidency, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Re: DRC'S Part-time, Pre-retirement Position for the Academic Year 1979-1980, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Axelrod, David (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Ashcroft, Neil (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Baker, Robert (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Birnbaum, Joel (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Bloch, Erich (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Astatine - Correspondence with D. Bloomer (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Bowen, E.G. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Buderi, Bob (Box 5, Folder 25a)
  - Correspondence - Bromley, Allen (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - Bucche, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Burak, David (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - Dick Crane, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - Devereux, Tony (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Downs, Donald (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - Eisner Thomas (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Forscher, Martin and Barrett Gallaghar (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - Barrett Gallaghar, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - Robert F. Gatje, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - Gingrich, Newell, 1974-1985 (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
  - Correspondence - Golden, William T. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - Greatbatch, Dr. Wilson (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - Ralph Helverson, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - Hoffman, Roald (Box 5, Folder 41-43)
  - Correspondence - Austin Kiplinger (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - Linowitz, Sol (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - Malott, Deane (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence - Marcham, John (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - Matyras, Robert (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence - McCall, Dan, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence - William McGuire, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - True McClean, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence - Floyd R. Newman, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence - Perkins, James (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence - Purcell, Robert (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence - Racker, Efraim (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence - Rawlings, Hunter (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence - Charles J. Reichert, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence - Rhodes, Frank (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Sampson, Harvey (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - William Sears, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Leslie R. Severinghaus, 1982-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Slater, E.C. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Tolani, N.P. (Box 6, Folder 6-13)
  - Correspondence - E.B. White, 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Phil Will, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Phil Will, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Kenneth Wilson, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Wilson, Robert (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Wriston Walter (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Admissions, 1977-1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Student Pugwash, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Plantations, 1980-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23-29)
  - Change of Status, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
  - Change of Status, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Resident Emeritus & Prof. Physics Emeritus (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Congratulatory Letters (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - Condolences and Get-well Letters (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Holiday Cards - Corson (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Holiday Letters (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Holiday Cards from Others (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Letters of recommendation
    - Recommendations, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Recommendations, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Recommendations, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Recommendations, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Recommendations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Recommendations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Recommendations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Recommendations, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Recommendations, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Recommendations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Recommendations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Recommendations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Recommendations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Recommendations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Recommendations, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Recommendations, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Recommendations, 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Recommendations - Jon Anderson, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Recommendations - Dr Thomas E. Baker, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Recommendations - Mark Barlow Jr., 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Recommendations - Cole Blasier, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Recommendations - Arthur W. Brodeur, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Recommendations - Joseph Bugliars, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Recommendations - Patricia J. Carry, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Recommendations - W. Dale Compton, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Recommendations - Ed T. Cranck, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Recommendations - Charles H. Dick, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Recommendations - Mildred S. Dresselhaus, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Recommendations - George Bradley Edmondson, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Recommendations - William A. Jenkins, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Recommendations - Barbara Kauber, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Recommendations - Austin Kiplinger, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Recommendations - David C. Knapp, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Recommendations - Douglas Martin (Deep Springs), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 41)